let's look at the solution for our speed
doubling quiz this is a period of 36
years if speed doubles every 2 years
that means that the speed has doubled 18
times so we have 2 to the 18th * 380 and
if you multiply this out it amounts to
about 99 million km/ hour and change in
reality the speed record for trains has
not even doubled between 1971 and 2007
the fastest thing that humankind ever
built is the Voyager 1 probe and its top
speed was
62,000 kmph if trains since
1971 followed speed doubling of
processors trains should have moved this
fast by
1996 so as you can see processors are
one of those rare things that have
observed speed doubling continuously for
many years and are still doing that